California ephemera collection, 1860-
California Ephemera Collection,
- Los Angeles Times (Boxes 168, 190, 255)
  Box 168 - 2 folders. Also *box 190, *203
  1. Los Angeles Times - Views. Box 255 is an oversize flat box, 21" x 25."
- Los Angeles Times Magazine (Box 282)
  June - November 2001
- Los Angeles Unified School District (Box 268)
- Los Angeles Workers School (Box 193)
- Los Angeles World Affairs Council (Box 66)
- Los Angeles Zoo (Box 243)
- Los Angeles, California (Boxes 48, 49, 161, 203, 239, 253)
  Box 49 - 5 folders. Box 239 - 2 folders.
- Los Angeles, California. Alumni Club. (Box 50)
- Los Angeles, California. Angel's Flight. (Boxes 50, 199)
- Los Angeles, California. Ballrooms (Box 221)
- Los Angeles, California. Bicentennial celebrations (Boxes 50, 199, 253)
  Also * 1. Los Angeles - History
- Los Angeles, California. Biography (Box 50)
  1. Los Angeles - History
- Los Angeles, California. Birmingham High School. (Box 50)
- Los Angeles, California. Bradbury Building (Box 268)
- Los Angeles, California. Bunker Hill. (Box 203)
- Los Angeles, California. Bureau of Power and Light. (Boxes 50, 161)
- Los Angeles, California. Bureau of Public Assistance. (Box 161)
- Los Angeles, California. Bureau of Sanitation. (Box 221)
- Los Angeles, California. Business cards and promotional material (Box 205)
- Los Angeles, California. California Science Center. (Boxes 239, 282)
- Los Angeles, California. Camera Pictorialists of Los Angeles. (Box 161)
- Los Angeles, California. Cathedral of Our Lady of the Angels (Box 268)
- Los Angeles, California. Centennial celebrations, etc. (Box 50)
  1. California - Centennial celebrations, etc.
- Los Angeles, California. Century City. (Boxes 161, 282)
  X. Century City.
- Los Angeles, California. Chamber of Commerce. (Box 161)
- Los Angeles, California. Chavez Ravine. (Box 239)
  - Chavez Ravine alarm! Torch-Reporter (September 1957)., Item No. 1 (Box 239, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, California. Chinatown. (Box 205)
  - Touring China Town, Los Angeles, California., ca. 1900(?).; Item No. 1 (Box 205, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, California. Churches (Boxes 51, 239, 282)
  - Mount Zion Baptist Church 50th anniversary program., May 1942.; Item No. 1 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    This program documents a community's long-term involvement in the Mount Zion Baptist Church, from the earliest days of its establishment to 1942. Includes numerous photographs of the committees of the congregation, and the names of past pastors.
- Los Angeles, California. Chutes Park. (Box 161)
- Los Angeles, California. City archives (Box 282)
- Los Angeles, California. City Charter, 1999. (Box 239)
- Los Angeles, California. City Clerk. (Box 205)
- Los Angeles, California. City planning (Box 282)
- Los Angeles, California. Civic Center. (Boxes 161, 199)
- Los Angeles, California. Civil Defense (Box 282)
- Los Angeles, California. Climate (Box 161)
- Los Angeles, California. Clubs (Box 51)
- Los Angeles, California. Clubs (Music) (Box 268)
- Los Angeles, California. Community services (Box 51)
- Los Angeles, California. Convention Center. (Boxes 221, 251)
- Los Angeles, California. Crematoriums (Box 268)
- Los Angeles, California. Crenshaw. (Box 195)
- Los Angeles, California. Cultural Affairs Department. (Boxes 188, 282)
- Los Angeles, California. Department of Airports. (Box 239)
- Los Angeles, California. Department of Animal Regulation. (Box 51)
- Los Angeles, California. Department of Building and Safety. (Box 221)
- Los Angeles, California. Department of City Planning. (Box 51)
- Los Angeles, California. Department of Neighborhood Empowerment (Box 268)
- Los Angeles, California. Department of Playgrounds and Recreation. (Box 51)
- Los Angeles, California. Department of Public Service. (Box 51)
- Los Angeles, California. Department of Public Works (Box 268)
- Los Angeles, California. Department of Recreation and Parks (Boxes 205, 239)
  Search also earlier headings: Los Angeles (Calif.) Department of Playgrounds and Recreation
- Los Angeles, California. Department of Transportation (Box 268)
- Los Angeles, California. Department of Water and Power. (Boxes 162, 239, 282)
- Los Angeles, California. Description and travel (Boxes 52, 213, 225, 269)
- Los Angeles, California. Downtown. (Boxes 225, 240)
- Los Angeles, California. Ebony Showcase Theatre (Box 269)
- Los Angeles, California. Echo Park. (Box 51)
- Los Angeles, California. El Capitan Theatre (Box 269)
- Los Angeles, California. Elysian Park. (Boxes 51, 282)
- Los Angeles, California. Emergency Preparedness Department (Box 269)
- Los Angeles, California. Farmers Market. (Box 52)
- Los Angeles, California. Festivals (Boxes 205, 251, 282)
- Los Angeles, California. Festivals, etc. (Box 51)
  - Speech, "Today is my birthday," given in Los Angeles., ca. 1956.; Item No. 1 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    Anonymous speech written from the perspective of the city of Los Angeles, for Los Angeles' 175th anniversary celebration. The speech mentions the importance of California's Spanish and Mexican heritage
- Los Angeles, California. Fire Department. (Box 52)
- Los Angeles, California. First Baptist Church. (Box 52)
- Los Angeles, California. First Methodist Church. (Box 52)
- Los Angeles, California. First Unitarian Church. (Box 128)
- Los Angeles, California. Fox International. (Box 186)
- Los Angeles, California. Fox Venice Theatre. (Box 52)
- Los Angeles, California. Freeways (Box 240)
- Los Angeles, California. Gilmore Stadium. (Box 192)
- Los Angeles, California. Greek Theatre. (Box 52)
- Los Angeles, California. Griffith Park. (Box 240)
- Los Angeles, California. Harbor. (Box 52)
  1. Los Angeles - Views (Harbor)
- Los Angeles, California. Hazard Park (Box 282)
- Los Angeles, California. Hermon (Box 269)
- Los Angeles, California. Highland Park (Box 282)
- Los Angeles, California. Historic houses, etc. (Box 162)
  1. Los Angeles. Cultural Heritage Foundation.
- Los Angeles, California. History (Box 53)
- Los Angeles, California. Hollenbeck Home for the Aged. (Box 54)
  See shelf list for subject and cross references.
- Los Angeles, California. Hollenbeck Park. (Box 54)
- Los Angeles, California. Hollywood High School. (Box 54)
- Los Angeles, California. Hospitals (Box 54)
  XX. Hospitals - California, Southern.
- Los Angeles, California. Hotels, taverns, etc. (Boxes 54, 240, 251, 282)
- Los Angeles, California. Huntington Park. (Box 203)
- Los Angeles, California. Immanuel Presbyterian Church. (Box 54)
- Los Angeles, California. Industries (Box 54)
- Los Angeles, California. Information Services Department. (Box 221)
- Los Angeles, California. John H. Francis Polytechnic High School. (Box 162)
- Los Angeles, California. Korea Town. (Box 240)
  - The Korea Times, Los Angeles, 30th Anniversary: 1969-1999., Item No. 1 (Box 240, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, California. Laemmle Theatres. (Box 162)
- Los Angeles, California. Landmarks (Box 283)
- Los Angeles, California. Le Conte Junion High School. (Box 162)
- Los Angeles, California. Lincoln Park. (Box 162)
- Los Angeles, California. Little Tokyo (Box 269)
- Los Angeles, California. Los Angeles Children's Museum. (Box 163)
- Los Angeles, California. Los Angeles High School. (Box 163)
- Los Angeles, California. Los Angeles State Historic Park (Box 282)
- Los Angeles, California. Los Angeles Theatre Center. (Box 186)
- Los Angeles, California. Los Feliz Theatre. (Box 192)
- Los Angeles, California. Los Feliz. (Box 240)
- Los Angeles, California. Maps (Boxes 205, 240, 261)
  - Bunker Hill and vicinity: analysis of present land uses and principal ownerships., June 1958.; Item No. 2 (Box 255, Folder 1)
    "Information contained hereon has been developed from reliable sources and is correct to the best of our knowledge and belief." "Over 50% of the entire Bunker Hill area is now being used for much needed PARKING LOTS serving downtown Los Angeles." Map covers area from Temple Street to the north, Hill Street to the east, Fifth Street to the south and the Harbor Freeway to the west.
- Los Angeles, California. Maps - 1932 Olympics (Box 261)
- Los Angeles, California. Mar Vista (Box 269)
- Los Angeles, California. Mayoral Race - 1993 (Box 195)
- Los Angeles, California. Metro. (Boxes 205, 206, 213, 230, 241, 252, 257, 263, 283)
  Box 206 - 3 folders. Box 230 - 5 folders. Box 241 - 5 folders. Box 241 - 5 folders. Box 263 - Poster by Frank Romero.
  Box 213 is an oversize flat box, 15" x 19". Box 263 is an oversize flat box, 26-1/2" x 33-1/2".
  - Art for rail transit: Metro Red Line segment one., ca. 1992.; Item No. 1 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    This brochure is about the art (and artists) that was commissioned for the stations of Metro Redline segment 1 which runs from Union Station to Westlake/MacArthur Park.
  - Datos del tunel., ca. 1992.; Item No. 2 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    A brochure for Spanish speaking residents with information on the forth coming Metro Rail project.
  - Tunnel trivia., ca. 1992.; Item No. 3 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    Information for Los Angeles residents on the forth coming Metro Rail project.
  - Linea Azul, centro de Los Angeles/Long Beach., ca. 1990.; Item No. 4 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Zero tolerance: Stop-Tag Zero Tolerance Program = Zero tolerance: Stop Tag Programa de Zero Tolerance., 1996.; Item No. 6 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Bus riders union [Union de usuarios]., 1996(?).; Item No. 7 (Box 206, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, California. Mission Village Tourist Court (Box 269)
- Los Angeles, California. Motion picture theatres (Box 196)
- Los Angeles, California. Municipal Art Department. Cultural Heritage Board. (Box 163)
- Los Angeles, California. Municipal Art Department. Municipal Art Commission. (Box 163)
- Los Angeles, California. Museum of Contemporary Art. (Box 163)
- Los Angeles, California. Museums (Boxes 56, 192)
  - The Old Plaza fire house, Los Angeles (Calif.)., undated.; Item No. 1 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    One-page summary of the Old Plaza fire house's history and restoration.
  - Dia de las Flores e Dia de las Camaras [Flower Day and Camera Day]., June 1971.; Item No. 2 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Small brochure advertising Flower Day and Camera Day on Olvera Street, Los Angeles. Local merchants dress in costume and decorate their stalls with flowers; visitors are encouraged to take photographs and submit them to a photo competition.
  - Old Los Angeles World Center., undated.; Item No. 3 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Promotional brochure for Old World Los Angeles, located near Olvera Street in downtown Los Angeles.
  - History of the Old Plaza Church and Olvera Street, Los Angeles (Calif.)., undated.; Item No. 4 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Brief history of the Old Plaza Church compiled by the author from his personal scrapbook of newspaper clippings.
- Los Angeles, California. Music Center (Boxes 55, 225)
- Los Angeles, California. Music Center - Ahmanson Theatre (Boxes 163, 240)
- Los Angeles, California. Music Center - Center Theatre Group (Box 269)
- Los Angeles, California. Music Center - Dorothy Chandler Pavilion (Box 55)
- Los Angeles, California. Music Center - Mark Taper Forum (Boxes 56, 240)
- Los Angeles, California. Music Center - Walt Disney Concert Hall (Box 269)
- Los Angeles, California. New Beverly Cinema. (Box 56)
- Los Angeles, California. New School for Social Research. (Box 56)
- Los Angeles, California. New Vagabond Theatre. (Box 56)
- Los Angeles, California. Nightclubs, Dance halls, etc. (Box 56)
- Los Angeles, California. Nuart Theatre. (Boxes 56, 252, 269)
- Los Angeles, California. Ostrich Farms. (Box 56)
- Los Angeles, California. Palisades High School. (Box 56)
- Los Angeles, California. Papal visit - 1987 (Box 283)
- Los Angeles, California. Park La Brea. (Box 163)
- Los Angeles, California. Parks (Box 56)
  X. Elysian Park. Los Angeles.
- Los Angeles, California. Pershing Square. (Box 56)
- Los Angeles, California. Personnel Department. (Box 221)
- Los Angeles, California. Pigeon Farm. (Box 56)
- Los Angeles, California. Plaza. (Boxes 56, 269)
- Los Angeles, California. Police Department. (Boxes 56, 269)
  X. Police - Los Angeles. Box 269 - LAPD coloring book.
  - Afro American Patrolmen's League bumper sticker., ca. 1970.; Item No. 1 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Los Angeles Police Department bumper sticker, possibly from a LAPD fraternal organization, that reads "I am my brother's keeper: be my brother."
  - Lady beware., ca. 1976.; Item No. 2 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Illustrated crime prevention brochure published by the Los Angeles Police Department, targeting white women. For comparison, see also the Spanish language version of this brochure, entitled "Damas, cuidado!"
  - Damas, cuidado! [Ladies, beware!]., ca. 1976.; Item No. 3 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Illustrated crime prevention brochure published by the Los Angeles Police Department, targeting Mexican American women. For comparison, see also the English language version of this brochure, entitled "Lady, beware!"
  - The Daily Bulletin: Department of Police, City of Los Angeles., June 29, 1915.; Item No. 4 (Folder 2)
  - Now that you've fought for peace...keep it: join the LAPD., ca. 1973.; Item No. 5 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Recruiting brochure issued by the Los Angeles Police Department, aimed towards Vietnam veterans.
- Los Angeles, California. Politics and government - 1965 - 1969 (Box 164)
- Los Angeles, California. Politics and government - 1970 (Box 57)
  - Tom Bradley mayoral campaign bumper sticker., 1970.; Item No. 1 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, California. Politics and government - 1971 - 1972 (Box 57)
- Los Angeles, California. Politics and government - 1973 - 1976 (Box 57)
  - Tom Bradley mayoral campaign bumper sticker ca. 1973., Item No. 1 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    First section image produced from digital copy of original document with personal information removed.
  - Your city? What will happen if the wrong man becomes mayor., ca. 1973.; Item No. 2 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Anti-Bradley mayoral campaign poster, designed for mailing, from the Committee to Re-elect Mayor Yorty. First section image produced from digital copy of original document with personal information removed.
  - Tom Bradley invites you to a party., January 12, 1973.; Item No. 3 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Flier advertising the opening of the Bradley for Mayor headquarters at 5615 Wilshire Boulevard.
  - Speakers Program presents Tom Bradley., February 28, 1973.; Item No. 4 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    UCLA flier advertising an address by Tom Bradley in the Ackerman Union Grand Ballroom.
  - Tom Bradley mayoral campaign letter., ca. 1973.; Item No. 5 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Open letter from the Committee to Elect Tom Bradley Mayor, highlighting Tom Bradley's accomplishments and qualifications for the Los Angeles mayoral office.
  - An inside look at Citizen Bradley: a Young Socialists for Rodriguez truth kit., ca. 1973.; Item No. 6 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Anti-Bradley political pamphlet summarizes Tom Bradley's record on social issues in Los Angeles, and comments on his position within the Democratic Party.
  - A great day in December: a celebration of Tom Bradley's first 500 days as Mayor of Los Angeles., December 11, 1974.; Item No. 7 (Folder 2)
- Los Angeles, California. Politics and government - 1977 - 1981 (Box 57)
- Los Angeles, California. Politics and government - 1982 - 1983 (Box 58)
- Los Angeles, California. Politics and government - 1984 - (Box 58)
- Los Angeles, California. Politics and government - 1992 (Box 188)
- Los Angeles, California. Politics and government - 1993 (Boxes 193, 196)
- Los Angeles, California. Politics and government - 1994 - (Box 205)
- Los Angeles, California. Politics and government - 1996 (Box 283)
- Los Angeles, California. Politics and government - 1998-1999 (Box 242)
- Los Angeles, California. Politics and government - 2000-2001 (Boxes 242, 269)
  Box 242 - 5 folders.
- Los Angeles, California. - Politics and government - 2001-2004 (Box 283)
- Los Angeles, California. - Politics and government - 2002 (Box 269)
- Los Angeles, California. - Politics and government - 2003 (Box 269)
- Los Angeles, California. - Politics and government - 2004 (Box 270)
- Los Angeles, California. - Politics and government - 2006 (Box 270)
- Los Angeles, California. - Politics and government - 2009 (Box 283)
- Los Angeles, California. - Politics and Government - to 1965. (Box 164)
  1. Los Angeles Today. A weekly journal of news and opinion.
- Los Angeles, California. Poundcake Hill. (Box 58)
  X. Poundcake Hill.
- Los Angeles, California. Produce Market. (Box 58)
  1. Los Angeles - Views (Produce Market)
- Los Angeles, California. - Race question (Box 58)
- Los Angeles, California. - Railroad stations (Box 58)
- Los Angeles, California. - Ralph Waldo Emerson Middle School (Box 270)
- Los Angeles, California. - Rancho Park Golf Course. (Box 205)
- Los Angeles, California. - Real estate (Boxes 240, 270, 283)
  Box 240 - 3 folders. Box 270 - 4 folders. Box 283 - 2 folders.
- Los Angeles, California. - Residences (Box 58)
- Los Angeles, California. - Restaurants (Box 283)
- Los Angeles, California. - Restaurants, lunchrooms, etc. (Boxes 58, 229, 260)
  Box 229 - 5 folders. Box 260 - 4 folders.
- Los Angeles, California. - Riots - 1965 (Box 163)
- Los Angeles, California. - Riots - 1992. (Boxes 190, 196)
  Box 190 - Includes Los Angeles Reader (8 May 1992) & LA Weekly (8-14 May 1992).
- Los Angeles, California. - School Children's Fiesta (Box 214)
  - School children's fiesta in Los Angeles: June 2, 3, 4, 5., June 1915.; Item No. 1 (Box 214, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, California. - Schools (Boxes 166, 199, 225, 243, 283)
  Box 166 also oversize. Box 225 is an oversize box, 15" x 19". Box 243 - 2 folders.
- Los Angeles, California. - Sherman Theatre. (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Silverlake. (Boxes 251, 284)
- Los Angeles, California. - Simon Wiesenthal Center. (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Southwest Museum. (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - St. Alban's Episcopal Church (Boxes 59, 165, 187, 217, 258)
  X. St. Alban's Episcopal Church. Box 217 - 4 folders. Box 258 - 4 folders.
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Adams Boulevard (Box 205)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Broadway (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Cahuenga Pass (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Chester Place (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Coldwater Canyon (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Commercial Street (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Figueroa Street (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Fremont Place (Box 205)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Larchmont Boulevard (Box 195)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Main Street (Box 60)
  1. Los Angeles, Calif. - Views - Main Street.
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Martin Luther King Boulevard (Box 243)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Olvera Street (Box 60)
  - Bienvenido, amigo!., undated.; Item No. 1 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Brochure advertising shops and restaurants in El Pueblo State Historic Park near Olvera Street, Los Angeles.
  - Casa la Golondrina., 1935.; Item No. 2 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Brochure advertising several spring festivals and events on Olvera Street, Los Angeles, and promoting Consuelo de Bonzo's Casa la Golondrina Mexican restaurant.
  - Walton and O'Rourke's Puppet Theatre ticket., undated.; Item No. 3 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    One complimentary pass for a performance of the Demi Tasse Revue at the Walton and O'Rourke's Puppet Theatre on Olvera Street, Los Angeles.
  - La Fiesta de la Reina (program)., August 2, 1934.; Item No. 4 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Tri-fold brochure advertising La Fiesta de la Reina, a celebration of the 165th anniversary of Los Angeles on Olvera Street.
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Sixth Street (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Spring Street (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Sunset Boulevard (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Ventura Boulevard (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Vermont Avenue (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streets - Wilshire Boulevard (Box 60)
- Los Angeles, California. - Streetscape Steering Committee (Box 270)
- Los Angeles, California. - Superior Court (Box 270)
- Los Angeles, California. - Temple Beth Am. (Box 61)
- Los Angeles, California. - The Institute of the American Musical. (Box 162)
  X. Institute of the American Musical. 1. Kreuger, Miles.
- Los Angeles, California. - Theatres (Boxes 243, 284)
  See also: Theatre - California - Los Angeles
- Los Angeles, California. - Tract maps (Box 205)
- Los Angeles, California. - Union Station. (Box 205)
- Los Angeles, California. - Urban planning (Box 61)
  - L.A. shows the world how to end slums., 1959.; Item No. 1 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Pamphlet highlights public official Gilbert E. Morris, and his promise to "end" slums throughout Los Angeles in 1959. Neighborhoods profiled include West Los Angeles, "Skid Row" near downtown, Pacoima, South Central, and Boyle Heights.
- Los Angeles, California. - Venice High School (Box 270)
- Los Angeles, California. - Views (Boxes 61, 253)
  1. Los Angeles, Calif. Chamber of Commerce. 2. Los Angeles, Calif. Public Library.
  Box 253 - Reproduction of 1873 lithograph.
- Los Angeles, California. - Vista Theatre. (Box 61)
- Los Angeles, California. - Watts Towers. (Boxes 61, 284)
- Los Angeles, California. - West Lake Park. (Box 61)
- Los Angeles, California. - Westdale (West Los Angeles) (Box 284)
- Los Angeles, California. - Wiltern Theatre (Box 270)
- Los Angeles, California. - Wrigley Field. (Box 61)
- Los Gatos, California (Boxes 66, 243)
- Los Molinos, California (Box 188)
- Los Olivos, California (Box 270)
- Lotusland. Santa Barbara, California (Box 270)
- Low, Frederick Ferdinand, 1829 - 1894 (Box 66)
- Lowe, Thaddeus Sobieski Coulincourt, 1832 - 1913 (Box 66)
- Loyola Marymount University. Los Angeles, California. (Box 270)
- Lucerne Valley, California (Box 221)
- Lugonia, California (Box 270)
- Lumbering - California (Box 66)
- Lummis, Charles Fletcher, 1859 - 1928 (Box 169)
- Lynwood, California (Box 66)
- Macdonald, J. Wiseman, 1866? - 1942 (Box 66)
- Madera County, California (Box 67)
- Madrona March. (Box 0)
- Madrona Marsh. Torrance, California (Box 270)
- Magic (Box 192)
- Magic Mountain. Valencia, California (Boxes 67, 284)
- Magill, A.E., 1842 - (Box 67)
  1. Magill, A.E., 1842 - - portrait.
- Magnin, Edgar Fogel, 1890 - 1984 (Box 67)
- Maguire, James G., 1853 - (Box 67)
- Maitri Foundation, Inc. (Box 67)
- Malibu, California (Box 67)
- Mammoth Lakes, California (Boxes 67, 284)
- Manhattan Beach, California (Box 244)
- Manhattan Beach, California - tract maps (Box 231)
  Box 231 is an oversize flat box, 21" x 25".
- Manly, William Lewis, 1820 - 1903 (Box 67)
- Mann, H.R., 1842 - (Box 67)
- Manteca, California (Box 189)
- Manufacturing industries - California - Los Angeles (Box 244)
- Manzanar National Historic Site. California (Box 271)
- Map Society of California (Box 67)
- March Field Museum. March Air Force Base, California (Box 222)
- Marcus, Graham (Box 190)
- Marin County, California (Boxes 169, 284)
- Marina Del Rey, California (Boxes 67, 284)
- Marine pollution - California (Box 271)
- Marineland of the Pacific, California (Box 67)
- Mariposa County, California (Box 67)
- Mariposa, California (Box 67)
- Markham, Edwin, 1852 - 1940 (Box 169)
- Markham, Henry Harrison, 1840 - 1923. (Box 67)
  1. Markham, Henry Harrison, 1840 - 1923 - portait.
- Markleeville, California (Box 284)
- Marshutz, S.G. (Box 67)
- Martial arts (Box 244)
- Martin Luther King, Jr. Day. Los Angeles, California. (Box 271)
- Martin, Everett Dean, 1880 - 1941 (Box 67)
- Marysville, California (Box 67)
- Mason, Biddy, 1818 - 1891 (Boxes 253, 253)
  - Grandma Biddy: Biddy Mason's Place, a midwife's homestead., c1988.; Item No. 1 (Box 197, Folder 3)